<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <channel>
        <title>生活反思 on Blank Space (en)</title>
        <link>http://tom789726.github.io/categories/life/</link>
        <description>Recent content in 生活反思 on Blank Space (en)</description>
        <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
        <language>en-us</language>
        <lastBuildDate>Sat, 08 Apr 2023 19:47:08 +0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://tom789726.github.io/categories/life/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" /><item>
        <title>Get yourself a channel to voice</title>
        <link>http://tom789726.github.io/blogs/public-relation/</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 08 Apr 2023 19:47:08 +0800</pubDate>
        
        <guid>http://tom789726.github.io/blogs/public-relation/</guid>
        <description>&lt;img src="http://tom789726.github.io/blogs/public-relation/sky.jpg" alt="Featured image of post Get yourself a channel to voice" /&gt;&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;a class=&#34;link&#34; href=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=dQw4w9WgXcQ&amp;amp;ab_channel=RickAstley&#34;  target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;
    &gt;Epiphany&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Stepping into the year of 2020 with the increasingly hectic conflicts on the cyber world, I have come to a realization that building a personal and public media platform is a must for any modern civilians. As the department of public relation has now become a fundamental and vital component for a company or even a government branch to smoothly operate, we should also set up our own ‘department of public relation’ to confront the more sinister environment of the internet war.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;YO&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;cite&#34;&gt;&lt;span&gt;― &lt;/span&gt;&lt;cite&gt;HAHA&lt;/cite&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The major reason that lead to such an inspiration is coming from the observation that a minor piece of rumour could gravely injure one’s bright future and having your own channel to express your view could become a helpful solution to shelter you from such damage. There comes a time when you are exposed to false accusations and you are trying desperately to explain yourself only to find out that it is futile and no one would listen to you. At this moment, you would be more than regret that you had not heeded the suggestion from an online anonymous author who told you that a personal media platform could be your life-saving straw. Not only could a self-owned media platform provides a way out upon emergency events, it could also help you gather influences online as your number of followers steadily grows.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The second reason why you should set up your own media platform is to blend in with a society that stresses self-promotion. Apart from getting a brief first impression from your resume, employers and their head-hunters are starting to notice that examining one’s social media is perhaps a more direct way to figure out whether you fit in their requirements or not. A virtually existing fancy front face that portrays positive personality (charisma) could definitely beat any contestants that lacks a well-managed social media profile even before the interview. A blog that shares food and travel experiences would convince people that you are enjoying your life, a column that constantly criticises on current events could show that you are in touch with the world and capable of delivering independent thinking. Hence, your boss would certainly be impressed by your charisma that differs depending on the nature of your media content.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;While building your brand on the internet could possibly promote your career in real-life, another major advantage would be attracting potential business collaborations. In the world of marketing, ‘customer reach’ has long been an influential indicator of a successful advertisement. Moving onto the digital age, popular blogs, YouTube channels and Facebook fanpages that could easily appear on the sight of millions have naturally become valuable assets that could be converted into cash. Although not everyone could be an internet celebrity, you could still get an opportunity of online marketing that target a specific group once you have accumulated enough amount of audience that matches this group.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Building your own media platform may seem to require immense works at first glance, but it would soon become a daily routine as time goes by. Whether it is the old-fashioned way of writing blogs on your own website, the more exhausting way of uploading creative contents onto your YouTube channel, or even the most casual way of leaving a few comments about sports, politics, anything you are interested in on your Facebook wall, could become the option of your own media platform. As long as you are paying efforts on creating meaningful contents to maintain the interest of your audience, there is no doubt that any form of public media could do the trick and this is by no chance an obstacle for the teenagers nowadays that have long been excelling in the knowledge of using the internet.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Conclusion&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;All in all, establishing a media platform that advocates your views or shares your interest would not really cost much while it could substantially benefits your quality of life by accumulating your own public media influence and defend any attacks that attempts to cripple one’s social state. Opportunity seldom knocks twice, and the best we can do is to equip ourselves with this new piece of weapon that could pave the way for success.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;bullet-points&#34;&gt;Bullet points&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Why should you own a media platform?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Protect you from rumors&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Positive lifestyle (Self-promotion)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Potential business platform (asset)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Develop a good habit of writing regularly&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Word count:&lt;/strong&gt; 694&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        </item>
        
    </channel>
</rss>
